So I told the haberdasher,
"You are not going to pawn off
last season's grosgrain on me."
And guess what I did next.
Oh, I bet you said something
a little bit cutting.
I did. I did indeed.
I told him where he could shove
his heinous
autumnal pumpkin ribbon.
Where the sun don't shine.
In the butt, right?
(laughs)
Oh, Carly,
I so enjoy our little chats.
-Aw, thanks. Me too.
(all scream)
How could you...
G2G! Bye, brother!
* I know *
* You see *
* Somehow the world
will change for me *
* And be so wonderful *
* So wake up
the members of my nation *
* It's your time to be *
* There's no chance
unless you take one *
* And the time to see
the brighter side *
* Of every situation *
* Some things are meant to be *
* So give your best
and leave the rest to me. *
Who am I? Where am I?
What am I?
Carly. Apartment.
Girl.
Nailed it.
Ho-ho, babe!
I got your texts asking me
to explain technology.
I am so flattered,
I dropped everything.
Millicent can take the bus.
God, it's hot when you ignore
your priorities for me.
I took the bus.
It was faster,
better for the environment
and I didn't have to make
small talk with the driver.
Win-win!
Now, from your texts,
it sounds like Carly
is the victim
of a deepfake.
Oh. The guy who turned in Nixon?
No.
Right?
A deepfake comes
from deep learning technology,
a type of A.I.
that creates algorithms
to do things like swap faces
to make realistic-looking
fake media.
Computers.
-Oh!
-Ah.
Millicent!
I wrote one of my signature
instructional tunes.
I know.
I kinda like those songs.
You're a regular Kidz Bop.
I just hope this doesn't mess
with your new product
that you had me stock up on.
* "D" is for your doppelganger
out in cyberspace... *
Babe, I love you, but shut up.
Wait, what new product?
This new product!
Tastes Famiglia!
The best pasta-based meat
alternative you've never tried.
I never posed for this.
But is that what I look like
when I shush people? (chuckles)
Nah, it's usually more like,
"Be quiet. Ugh."
(laughs): Wow.
That was spot-on.
Not.
"Carly Shay says,
'Tastes Famiglia mimics
"'the sturdiness of meat
with the plush mouthfeel
of pasta.'"
"Mouthfeel"? Ugh.
You disgust me.
Guys, this... (chuckles)
obviously isn't me.
I use napkins.
Oh, my God.
Someone is using fake me
to sell fake meat.
This is a crime.
-Maybe we should call the cops?
-Yeah.
(laughs)
Oh, you're serious?
Of course he is.
* When the situation's
not that fun *
* Just pick up a phone,
dial 911. *
Remember when someone
in my comments threatened
to "find me and wear me"?
-Yeah, but that was...
-Not done.
The cops said it didn't count
because it happened in my phone.
(scoffs)
But surely...
Still going.
Then he texted me, "Carly Shay,
I'm coming to get you
at the Bushwell."
And the police said-- quote--
"This could be about anyone."
Look, I know this sucks,
but, like I always tell
Millicent...
* When life
gives you lemons... *
Be quiet! Ugh.
Hey, Meat-stagroupies.
I'm here at Shay What?!
to try...
Tastes Family,
the best pasta-based meat
alternative I've never tried.
(gagging)
You!
(retching)
Tastes Famiglia is blowing up,
but now Shay What?! customers
are throwing up.
So,
you got a little ditty
for this one?
I do not.
"
Man, Carly's going through it.
Which one's Carly?
The little girl?
No, the one that I live with.
You live with a child?
She does love a bib
and a bedtime story.
I'm so glad your bestie's
finally in town.
I just hope you don't
love him more than me.
-Oh. (chuckles): Harper!
-(chuckles)
I'm not ready
to make that decision.
-(laughs) Oh!
-(doorbell rings)
Do I look all right?
Dimitri-Pascual used to work
the counter at Neiman's.
Oh, he sold clothes?
No. He just gave
his unsolicited opinions.
And charged for them.
-Hey, girl, hey!
-(giggling)
DIMITRI-PASCUAL and TINSLEY:
Walk, walk,
walk, walk, walk, pose!
(laughing)
Ew.
-That'll be ten dollars.
(laughs)
-(laughs)
Harper, I want you to meet
my ride-or-die, Dimitri-Pascual.
-(chuckles)
-He's like Madonna.
-No. Last. Name. (laughs)
-(chuckling)
-Oh! Mwah. Mwah.
-Mwah. Mwah.
Mwah. Mwah.
OMG, you are serving
disgusting, queen.
(chuckles)
I hope you catch
chlamydia from a koala.
(Tinsley chuckles)
(quietly): Does this man think
I have unsafe sex with koalas?
-Absolutely not.
It's a compliment.
-(chuckles)
-Dimitri-Pascual
loves marsupials.
-(chuckles)
Zoology. Look it up,
you dumb whore.
-It's a compliment!
(laughing)
Thank you for cooking.
But this looks like it was
thrown up by an old person.
Walk?
-Walk. (chuckles)
-(chuckles)
BOTH;
Walk,
walk, walk, walk, walk.
You know who else
had no last name?!
Satan.
Good afternoon, Carly Nation.
I interrupt your day
with terrible news.
I, Carly Shay,
am the victim of a deepfake.
I'll let that sink in.
Tastes Famiglia
is not endorsed by me.
Guys,
Deepfake Carly wants
to join my live!
Let her in
so you can confront her.
And I can try
and tell 'em apart.
Tell her I said hi.
What? She may be a fraud,
but she's still my sister.
My fraud sister.
My fister!
Hello, Deepfake Carly.
Looks like you finally decided
to show my face.
Oh, Carly, I'm the real Carly.
And I, Carly,
have nothing to hide.
You're the charlatan.
God, she always uses
the coolest words.
Two of them.
I don't want it
and yet I can't look away.
I have cold, hard evidence
that proves
I am the one true Carly Shay.
To begin, I'll reveal something
only the real Carly would know.
My first celebrity crush
was Foghorn Leghorn.
What? No.
I never had lustful yearnings
for a shapely cartoon rooster!
Shapely?
And to prove it,
I'd like to share
some of my Fog-Leg erotica.
(chuckles, clears throat)
"It was a quiet night
in the henhouse when..."
Bye!
Who would do this to me?
Everybody likes me.
Except for Lewbert.
And Ms. Briggs,
Wade Collins, Griffin...
Kyoko and Yuki,
all the Pet-ographers...
Wes, Beau, me.
Should I just go get my binder?
Okay, fine.
I guess a few people
have minor qualms with me.
But...
who would go
to all this trouble?
I mean, it's so elaborate.
It's so evil. It's so...
-Nevel Papperman!
-Mayor Pete Buttigieg!
Nevel Papperman.
I can't believe Nevel invited us
to an evil lair
with no street parking.
Why is there so much cured meat?
Because he's a thoughtful host?
Well, well, well.
Carly Shay et al.
Allow me to explain.
(imitates Vito Corleone):
There have been two great loves
of my life:
my beloved wife Prunella
and The Godfather,
a film...
I have never seen.
(normal voice):
Such a fun vibe though.
Start with the third one.
The first two are garbage.
(squeals)
Carly Shay!
Hi!
Oh, my God!
I haven't seen you
since you were my bridesmaid.
Isn't that crazy?
I miss you so much!
How have you been, Mama?
Not great, Prunella.
Nevel, you need to stop this.
People are getting sick.
More importantly,
my restaurant got shut down!
For two hours!
Is this all because
I ruined your wedding?
Ruined?
I thought our wedding was great.
I seem to remember one
very handsome blond bombshell
who proved to be
quite agile at the limbo.
It's in the hips.
But you failed to give us a gift
within one year's time.
And, per Emily Post,
you are punished.
Wait. Let me get this straight.
So you manufactured
a toxic vegan product,
plastered my face all over it
and then deepfaked me
to get my brother to sell it,
all because you had to buy
your own freakin' KitchenAid?
Ooh!
What color did you guys get?
-Oh. Rose gold.
-That is so classy.
-Did you get
the pasta attachments?
-Oh, my God, did you make
-this sausage
with the meat grinder?
-Guys!
Look, this is ridiculous.
But I'll get you something if
it means you'll leave me alone.
Something? Carly,
you can't go off-registry.
Society has rules.
Fine. What's left?
Oh, my God.
A "Mess with Carly" fund?
Some couples do honey funds,
but we honeymooned
at Grandpappa Papperman's
palatial Polynesian palapa.
So we launched a "Mess
with Carly" fund instead.
-(chuckles)
-(chuckles) You see,
when this all began,
it was my love's elaborate
scheme to exact revenge.
But then we realized
we were having
the best sex of our lives,
and now it's just our thing.
Did anyone get you guys
a melon baller?
What I wouldn't give
to wrap this
around a fresh hunk
of cantaloupe right now.
We used the Carly fund
to buy the rancid pork
in Tastes Famiglia.
Great price, too.
They were practically
throwing it away.
(laughs)
Did you say "rancid pork?"
-Uh-huh.
Enough of this.
There is nothing you can do
to get us to stop.
Nothing! (cackles)
(laughs, growls)
Pruney, your evil laugh
is getting so sinister.
Oh. I learned from the best.
If there's nothing I can do
to stop you,
then why did you make us
come all the way down here?
'Cause seeing you squirm
is really doing it for us.
(laughs)
(both cackling)
Spencer, why are you laughing?
I'm very uncomfortable!
So, during orientation
of freshman year,
I threw an epic rager
in her room,
and when the campus cops came,
I told them that
the alcohol was Tinsley's,
and this delinquent slut
got put in front
of the disciplinary committee.
(laughs)
And you thought,
"This is a person
I want to be friends with."
No, no, no, it was funny.
Daddy got LMFAO
to speak at graduation,
and it all went away.
Well, if you had
done that to me,
you'd have graduated
to the cemetery.
I'm gonna go grab another drink.
But you still have so much left.
Mm. Not anymore.
I'll keep you company.
If I said I was
going to pee instead,
-would that stop you?
-Nope.
So, Dimitri-Pascual.
-Mm-hmm.
-Two first names.
Got to be a story there.
Mmm, the story is:
I'm gonna kill you.
The end.
Feels a little light
in the middle.
You're kidding, right?
I'm not.
You see, when Tinsley's single,
she spoils me rotten like
the little princeling that I am.
I'm like her child
and her boyfriend
all rolled into one.
Well, I'm her girlfriend,
and our dynamic is normal,
so you and I need to coexist.
Oh, I don't coexist with anyone.
Just ask Cherry Jones.
Spencer's cool revenge
idea number 48:
I marry Nevel's mother
and put him up for adoption.
No need to get
family courts involved.
They're busy enough.
Spencer's cool revenge
idea number 49:
We fill Nevel's car
with Livestrong bracelets.
How many Livestrong bracelets
did you buy?
I thought I was helping.
Look, Nevel
and Prunella are just
trying to get a rise out of me,
so I'm ignoring them
and letting the chips
fall where they may.
Fall, chips, fall.
Ooh, Carly.
You got to see this live.
Looking for a cure to solve
all your ailments?
Then I, Freddie Benson,
have the answer for you.
Tastes Famiglia.
Endorsed by me, Freddie Benson.
Thank God I never
took his last name.
If you lack bladder control--
and I know I do--
bang! Tastes Famiglia.
And if you have
head-to-toe dry skin...
-And there goes his shirt.
-I know I do.
Wow, he is surprisingly jacked.
* D is for your doppelganger
out in cyberspace *
* "E" is for... *
Ew, that's me!
Oh yeah, baby,
that's nice.
Okay, obviously that
is also a deepfake.
But I do love what
they did with my torso.
Aah!
Game over, bitch.
Oh, I'm sorry, Millicent.
That wasn't to you.
First they came for me,
I was fine.
Then they came for my brother.
-Also fine.
-Wha...
But now they come for my man?
My sweet, defenseless
little man?
I'm a yellow belt.
Hear my battle cry!
(shrieks)
Here's the plan.
We'll surround them
at the warehouse.
Spencer, at this point,
you'll already have wrangled
all the schnauzers.
Where did you get this egg?
It's very important that I know.
Once we get them
out of the warehouse,
Harper, you'll need to blindfold
and handcuff them immediately.
Got it. The only handcuffs
I have are pink and fuzzy.
Will that work?
Can people get out of them?
Only if they use
their safe word.
Perfect.
Freddie,
you'll knock 'em out
with chlorophyll.
I think you mean chloroform.
I mean, what?
Do we know anyone
with a really big trunk
and access to a landfill?
Okay, honey, I'm gonna
stop you right there.
Oh, please, Freddie,
we could never fit
a whole body into your Yaris.
It barely gets off
the ground with groceries.
While I love this aggro energy,
we do not need to do
an actual murder.
Okay?
We just...
we just need to
get into their heads.
And I think I know how.
-With a drill?
-Yes!
(cheering)
Okay,
everyone needs
to take off the camo.
(groaning)
Sorry I didn't exactly hit
it off with Dimitri-Pascual.
But it's nice to have
some alone time again.
Why are you setting
a third plate?
I'm not.
-I didn't.
-(doorbell rings)
I did.
Hey, hags.
Tinsley told me you got
a little bit in your feels,
so I made you a "sorry you have
no sense of humor" casserole.
I'm kidding.
I'm laughing.
I'm so glad you're both
open to try again.
It means a lot to me.
Oh, I would do anything for you,
my putrid little hellhound.
Why don't you make like
the kitchen wench you are
and grab us some sporks?
(laughs)
It's so sweet of you
to spend your last night in town
at my humble abode.
Humble is the perfect
word for it.
Oh!
(laughs)
Ooh, "cheese-ay."
I thought you were vegan?
Or is that just
one of your phases,
like coffee enemas or clowning?
It is vegan, but you won't
even be able to tell
because it has
the sturdiness of meat.
Sturdiness?
And the plush
mouthfeel of pasta.
Mouthfeel?
Does it also cure
a variety of ailments?
Well, why don't you take
a bite and find out?
Well, in my culture,
the chef always
takes the first bite.
Well, in my nearby,
adjacent culture,
the chef watches in delight
as the host takes the first bite
and swallows it.
Since it's my home...
I'm starving,
so if you don't mind,
I'm just gonna dive right in.
(distorted):
No!
(distorted): No!
You can't eat that, Tinsley.
It's Tastes Famiglia,
so it's disgusting.
Not in a good way.
And it might murder you.
-Also not in a good way.
-(Tinsley gasps)
Is this true?
Are you trying to poison me?
Tins, I would never.
I was trying to poison her.
Oh!
(exclaims)
I'm gonna say something to you
I should have said
a long time ago.
You're not funny
and I want you
out of my life, Andrew.
(gasps)
But-but-but,
without me, you're
just another rich bitch.
-Oh.
-I am
the Leah Remini to your J.Lo.
I am the LeFou to your Gaston.
Well, she's
a rich bitch in love.
Rejection.
Look it up, you dumb whore.
Oh, Harper.
I should have trusted you
about Dimitri-Pascual.
I am gonna miss him, though.
Who's gonna call me
a ghastly little troll now?
I will.
Because I'm your girlfriend.
And our dynamic is normal.
(gasps)
-What is it?
-I think I owe Cherry Jones
a huge apology.
We are the masterminds
behind Tastes Famiglia.
I rue the day I ever ruined
Carly's credibility.
Hey, that's my line.
Oh, my God,
but it's so fun to say.
"Rue." Yeah, it is. (chuckles)
In our defense,
messing with Carly et al
really spiced up our sex life.
Which we needed.
I mean, I really just
lie there like a starfish.
You'd think two evil geniuses
would be dynamos in the sack.
But you would be wrong.
In conclusion,
we're bad at sex,
and we're very sorry.
And cut.
And gross.
That is a wrap on iCarly's
first deepfake operation.
And our last, God willing.
I'd actually love another take
now that I've had a run at it.
And now we wait.
(phone chimes)
Ooh, that was quick.
Nevel says
they'll stop if we stop.
(laughs)
And also, he's very virile.
-(phone chimes)
-Like a cobra.
-A cobra with a sex addiction.
-(groans)
-(phone chimes)
But only for his wife.
Aw. Good for them.
Pruney, no.
I can change.
Or stay the same.
Whatever you want.
I haven't really been listening.
Messing with Carly
was all we had.
Now that that's over,
so are we.
And I'm taking the KitchenAid.
With the pasta attachment?
How will I extrude?
I mean, don't go.
I love you.
Ugh!
(gasps)
"Here's a wedding gift
to keep things spicy.
"Do not contact me.
Carly Shay."
What do you say--
should we give it another shot?
Let's get the limbo stick, baby.
Ooh!